http://www.monroeccc.edu/privacy-statement

Cookies
You have the option of disabling cookies by changing the preferences on your browser, and you will still be able to use certain sections of our site. However, you will not be able to use any parts of this site that require a login.
Third-Party Tracking Technology
This website uses a tracking technology called Google Analytics to obtain site usage information such as users’ Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet domain and host names, browser software, and the date and time site is visited. Data obtained through Google Analytics does not include and is not linked to any personal information. Data from Google Analytics allows us to monitor the use of this website, understand how users find it and improve its function and content.
Site usage data collected through Google Analytics is not shared with other Google products and tools. Our use of Google Analytics is in compliance with Google’s Terms of Service and MCCC’s own guidelines. Google provides more information about Google’s privacy practices and information on how to opt out of Google Analytics tracking of your web browsing at https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html.
Server Logs
Our web servers routinely generate logs that contain the following types of information each time the website is used:
The date, time and length of your visit.
The path taken through our site and the browser being used.
The list of files downloaded and the amount of time spent viewing video or audio files.
The IP Address of the computer accessing our website.
Any errors encountered.
This information is used primarily to monitor the functioning and integrity of the website.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we do not control or claim any responsibility for the privacy practices or content of other websites. We encourage users to read the privacy statements of each website they visit.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to receive or not receive communications from Monroe County Community College College. However, at this time this website does not manage or send communications.
Changes to Privacy Statement
We reserve the right to alter or amend this privacy statement at any time and without prior notice. If we make changes to our privacy statement, we will indicate this on our home page.
Disclaimer
Neither Monroe County Community College, nor any of its units, programs, employees, agents or individual trustees, shall be liable for any improper or incorrect use of information obtained through the use of this website
Consent
By using this website, you consent to the terms of this privacy statement.
Questions and Feedback
Your questions, comments and concerns are always welcome. Please send us your feedback regarding the privacy statement or any other issues.  Contact info can be found at https://www.monroeccc.edu/communications.
Request Info
Visit Campus
Apply Now
Give to MCCC
Connect with MCCC:
Facebook Link
Twitter Link
Instagram Link
YouTube Link
